Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary!
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day,
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first. I'll
hurt it. Be so bad.
I could burst.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We go.
Hurry!
Come on! Really?
I was having fun, but now
they're all too chicken to fight!
I'll blame them!
I am pretty awesome!
Well, might as well knock out their
officers while they're gone, right?
Woo!
Awkward!
Cookie cutter!
Hey, come in, Commander Chopper!
I'm guessing it's not supposed
to be shaking like that, right?
What's up?
I think I'm home!
It serves you right.
I call that one the Drum Drop.
Ow.
Yeah, yeah.
While you morons were shooting at nothing,
I dug a whole maze of
tunnels under this place.
Hey!
Where'd you go?
Koza!
JUMPER!
Perfect!
Now all I have to do is trick
their biker buddy into -
What the hell?
Who put a sinkhole here?
What?
How stupid are you?
That hurt.
Yeah, you're telling me
that was a pretty big drop.
You just made a super mistake short stuff
Everybody off the tank?
Franky why did you throw us out like that!
Sorry, but the next form
has only got one seat.
Let's get freaky
You're freaky enough already
Stand by!
Whoa!
Super Freaky!
Hold your applause!
Brachiotak first!
Headshaves!
Brachiotank 5!
Black Rhino F .R .U. 4!
Docking phase!
Whoa! So good! Headshaves!
Meet the Iron Pirate!
Giri Randy
This is crazy.
No way!
We'd rather get a giant fighting robot.
This is a dream come true.
I still haven't met the
mad genius Vegapunk,
but I finally made his dream come true.
Even if it did take a whole
two years of trial and error,
By manipulating the shaped memory
alloy known as waffle metal,
I've built a big-ass robot!
Come on, men!
It's just a bucket of foam!
Whoa!
Look at him go!
Oh, I'm just getting started, bro!
This thing is called
the Plunderer's Sword!
Franky!
There's a sword, too!
General!
Watch your step!
He's sweating low!
You whims can jump up
and down all you want,
and I'll blast you
straight out of the sky!
Whee!
I want shoulder cannon!
Franky Cannon!
Not what I was expecting!
But hey... Hey!
It's still cool, though!
Damn this guy. What now?
General Wings!
That's right, Franky! You're a boost!
Looks lame to me.
Hey, you must be one of
the weaker ones, huh?
Who says I'm weak?
I just like it when other
people do all the work.
Sorcery Climb Attacked.
This one is gonna blow you away.
Time for the Gustsor.
I learned that back in Weatheria.
That's hardcore meteorology.
Now who's weak?
Wait a sec, where's Chopper?
Come on, let's get that guy over there!
Oh man, guess I'm
officially off the tank now.
Guess I've got to fight by myself.
You don't scare me!
I'm not some little
weenie like I was before!
Special attack, Greenside!
Bamboo Javelin!
I hope you're proud, Master!
I'll never forget those two crazy years I
spent training with you
in the swindling forest.
This is the next chapter of life!
The legend of the great hero Usopp
is beginning right here and now.
I'm gonna dig sinkholes
all over this plaza!
It doesn't matter how powerful
that ridiculous robot is.
If he drives into a
hole then it's all over.
What's that noise?
That can't be right.
Sounds like someone else is here.
He shot straight out of the ground.
Who are you?
Look close.
I can dig holes, too.
My horn point really came in handy, huh?
That's cool.
Wow, you can turn into a big
hairy bug and you never told me?
Oh, that is so rude.
You should know.
I spent the last two years working on
all seven of my transformation points.
Now I'm so good that I only need
the rumble ball for one of them!
So I can use all my other
forms whenever I want to.
You coral head pain in the ass?
I'm so gonna bite you!
They're not coral, they're
horns like a monster.
And you are about to see
what this monster can do.
How many have we killed?
Not a single one.
My Kraken!
I don't know what you did to gain Straw
Hat's trust, but that doesn't matter.
You might salvage this yet.
You've got the princess where I want her.
Now squeeze the life out of her, will you?
Did you perhaps forget your
brother at the North Pole?
I know exactly where he is right now.
My men and I can go there and
slaughter him any time we please!
I wouldn't mind killing
you or your family.
The corpses of mythical
beasts are quite valuable.
But that won't be a problem
because you're on my side, right?
It's your choice.
What?
So the Kraken agreed to do Hordy's breading
to ensure the safety of his brother?
This is your last chance.
I said squeeze that mermaid to death now!
Please, Tsurume, stop
it, you're hurting me!
Tsurume!
You wanted to save your brother's life,
So you did whatever this jerk told you?
I know what that's like.
So, is he your big brother
or your little brother?
If you need someone to
save him, then count on me!
Just ask next time.
After all, we're friends, right?
It's coming this way let's get
You're no match for our
leader leave this one to me?
We won't let you get one
step closer to our captain!
Back off.
You go through me first.
We have to stop Straw Hat!
Alright, second gear!
Hey, where'd he go?
That's enough!
I'm done with you!
It can't be.
That's the ship of promise.
I...
I don't understand.
Why is it moving?
Who is doing this and how?
This is a terrible development.
You must forgive my ignorance,
father, but I don't understand why
you're so upset by its presence.
Well, I do admit that it's strange.
The ship itself is
nothing more than a relic.
It has no purpose today.
You're wrong.
We can't afford to have
anything happen to that ship.
You see, my son, until the intended day,
that vessel was not to be
moved from its resting place.
Are you okay, Captain?
I thought after he took all those energy
steroids, nothing could stand up to him.
Wait, what's happening?
Little bastard.
Well, we got back up.
This guy's tough.
I've had enough.
My face, my karate will end you.
He knocked his head off.
And all it took was a single blow!
Guess you forgot!
I'm made of rubber!
Now that it matters with a punch that
weak, you're nothing compared to Jinbei!
Of course he's not!
Rather than improve, he
relies on false strength!
Time for head hardening!
Higher chill squad, form up!
Bring it on!
Your head's gonna split wide open!
You wouldn't be so sure about that!
Bum-Bum-Bum!
He just gets at their
shields with his face!
Armament hardening!
I was not doing that!
Can he see into the future or what?
I wish he would teach me that.
He's using observation Haki.
I think I've done more than
enough dancing around for one day.
GONG GONG MULLET!
I can't believe it.
He's so small but so strong.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about. But how?
I've seen pirates before.
None of them could do stuff like that.
Huh?
It...
it can't be!
That's the Noah from the Fishman District!
Why is it flying above the island?
What's it doing here?
If you ask me, it looks like
it's going to the plaza.
It's almost broken through the
bubble protecting the island.
Once that thing pops,
we're all goners for sure.
We'll be sent to watery graves!
Wanna fill me in?
It's the Noah!
Whoa!
That thing is super gigantic!
If that ship hits us, the island
isn't gonna stand a chance!
Whoever's operating it needs to pull back!
They can't!
It doesn't have an engine!
There is no way that this will
end well for us! It's okay!
This is it!
We're dead for sure this time!
In our last moments, I
can't help but wonder,
will our blood be enough
to stain the sea red?
Can you not say morbid
things like that right now?
Let's make a break for it!
Get into the water while you can't!
Wait!
Wait, everyone!
Look up there!
Why do I gotta be so clumsy?
That's one of Vander
Decken's men. Watatsumi!
Captain Decken, can you hear me up there?
I fell off to knowing I can't get back!
You have to stop that ship for me!
I don't want to die down here!
Wait a moment.
Deccan's behind this.
Hey, Captain Hardy!
Are you okay?
Also, I'm curious if this is
a part of your plan, maybe?
I mean, it could be because Deccan
is controlling the ship, but...
Will you shut up?
I'm busy here.
Damn you.
I'll kill you, Straw Hat. Wow.
I really didn't think you'd
get back up after that one.
I guess this guy's no joke after all.
Is he out of his mind?
What the hell is Deccan thinking?
That bastard is about to
ruin all my hard work!
I am offering my love one last time!
Get the dick away!
How do I not die?
Sorry, pal.
You should have thought about
not dying before you fell off.
Them's the brakes.
You're just one more thing I have to
sacrifice in my pursuit of Shura Hachi.
He's out!
Why is this happening?
The bubble's about to pop.
We're doomed for sure.
Hey where did princess Shirahoshi go?
She vanished this.
Isn't good princess?
Please you have to come back.
What's this?
My Shirahoshi has disappeared.
No not now.
I'm right here!
Princess Shirahoshi!
When'd she get up there?
Please don't die!
Come back down!
What do you think you're doing?
She's changing the ship's trajectory
by moving herself away from the island.
What?
Now that's exactly what I'd
expect from my dream girl!
I knew you were awful!
But I never believed you
would stoop this low!
No!
If you want to take my life,
then I am powerless to stop you!
But no one else should have to suffer!
I won't let you harm this kingdom!
I will protect it with my life!
So come get me, you monster!
Princess!
No!
Figures.
That's what I get for
teaming up with a madman.
I expected he might kill a few commoners,
but now I see he just
as soon killed me too.
Hmm.
I won't stand for betrayal.
Please!
Don't sacrifice yourself for us!
We have to do something to save her!
Lovely!
Your beauty is so much
more than skin teeth.
Faced with impossible odds,
you take matters into your own hands
to save the countless citizens.
I hope to crash for no good reason.
Ah!
You're a whole day!
This is so unfair.
As I always suspected,
you are the perfect woman?
to become Mrs.
Vanderdeck in the ninth.
But since you insist on rejecting me,
I fear your beauty must
be resigned to history.
Now die!
Please run away!
Dammit, weepy Hachi!
I told you to stay
where I can protect you!
He's trying to get away!
Captain Horny!
What the hell?
Where did the captain run off to?
Look up there!
He's on that chain!
He's making a break for the Nami!
I'll show you what happens
to trainers, Fandertekin.
But I do admit, I like
this idea, of course.
Unforgivable.
I'll make him pay for
hurting the princess.
Saint, hold it! I'll go!
You take care of the plaza!
Are you sure?
Think about it, Luffy.
The ship's in the water.
Put the ship's in a bubble,
so it should be okay.
That would make sense.
Deccan is weak to seawater, just like you.
Despite being a fish man, he
needs air to move around freely.
Better safe than sorry, though.
Take this bubbly coral.
Good call.
I can't believe I'm
letting you save the girl.
You better not let us down!
Don't hold anything back, Luffy!
Here I go!